[
    {
        "Front": "あ",
        "Back": "Ah",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ああ",
        "Back": "like that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あいさつ・する",
        "Back": "to greet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "間",
        "Back": "a space",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "Front": "合う",
        "Back": "to match",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "Front": "あかちゃん",
        "Back": "infant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "上る",
        "Back": "to rise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "Front": "赤ん坊",
        "Back": "baby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "Front": "空く",
        "Back": "to open, to become empty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 4
    },
    {
        "Front": "アクセサリー",
        "Back": "accessory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "あげる",
        "Back": "to give",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "浅い",
        "Back": "shallow,superficial",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 5
    },
    {
        "Front": "味",
        "Back": "flavour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 6
    },
    {
        "Front": "アジア",
        "Back": "Asia",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "明日",
        "Back": "tomorrow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 7
    },
    {
        "Front": "遊び",
        "Back": "play",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 8
    },
    {
        "Front": "集る",
        "Back": "to gather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 9
    },
    {
        "Front": "集める",
        "Back": "to collect something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 10
    },
    {
        "Front": "アナウンサー",
        "Back": "announcer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アフリカ",
        "Back": "Africa",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アメリカ",
        "Back": "America",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "謝る",
        "Back": "to apologize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 11
    },
    {
        "Front": "アルコール",
        "Back": "alcohol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "アルバイト",
        "Back": "part-time job",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "安心",
        "Back": "relief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 12
    },
    {
        "Front": "安全",
        "Back": "safety",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 13
    },
    {
        "Front": "あんな",
        "Back": "such",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "案内",
        "Back": "to guide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 14
    },
    {
        "Front": "以下",
        "Back": "less than",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 15
    },
    {
        "Front": "以外",
        "Back": "with the exception of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 16
    },
    {
        "Front": "医学",
        "Back": "medical science",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 17
    },
    {
        "Front": "生きる",
        "Back": "to live",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 18
    },
    {
        "Front": "意見",
        "Back": "opinion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 19
    },
    {
        "Front": "石",
        "Back": "stone",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 20
    },
    {
        "Front": "いじめる",
        "Back": "to tease",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "以上",
        "Back": "more than,this is all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 21
    },
    {
        "Front": "急ぐ",
        "Back": "to hurry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 22
    },
    {
        "Front": "致す",
        "Back": "(humble) to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 23
    },
    {
        "Front": "いただく",
        "Back": "(humble) to receive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "一度",
        "Back": "once",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 24
    },
    {
        "Front": "一生懸命",
        "Back": "with utmost effort",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 25
    },
    {
        "Front": "いっぱい",
        "Back": "full",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "糸",
        "Back": "thread",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 26
    },
    {
        "Front": "以内",
        "Back": "within",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 27
    },
    {
        "Front": "田舎",
        "Back": "countryside",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 28
    },
    {
        "Front": "祈る",
        "Back": "to pray",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 29
    },
    {
        "Front": "いらっしゃる",
        "Back": "(respectful) to be,to come or to go",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "植える",
        "Back": "to plant,to grow",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 30
    },
    {
        "Front": "うかがう",
        "Back": "to visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "受付",
        "Back": "receipt",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 31
    },
    {
        "Front": "受ける",
        "Back": "to take a lesson or test",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 32
    },
    {
        "Front": "動く",
        "Back": "to move",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 33
    },
    {
        "Front": "うそ",
        "Back": "a lie",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "うち",
        "Back": "within",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "打つ",
        "Back": "to hit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 34
    },
    {
        "Front": "美しい",
        "Back": "beautiful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 35
    },
    {
        "Front": "写す",
        "Back": "to copy or photograph",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 36
    },
    {
        "Front": "移る",
        "Back": "to move house or transfer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 37
    },
    {
        "Front": "腕",
        "Back": "arm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 38
    },
    {
        "Front": "うまい",
        "Back": "delicious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "裏",
        "Back": "reverse side",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 39
    },
    {
        "Front": "売り場",
        "Back": "place where things are sold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 40
    },
    {
        "Front": "うれしい",
        "Back": "glad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "うん",
        "Back": "(informal) yes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "運転",
        "Back": "to drive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 41
    },
    {
        "Front": "運転手",
        "Back": "driver",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 42
    },
    {
        "Front": "運動",
        "Back": "to exercise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 43
    },
    {
        "Front": "エスカレーター",
        "Back": "escalator",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "枝",
        "Back": "branch, twig",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 44
    },
    {
        "Front": "選ぶ",
        "Back": "to choose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 45
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠慮",
        "Back": "to be reserved, to be restrained",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 46
    },
    {
        "Front": "おいでになる",
        "Back": "(respectful) to be",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "お祝い",
        "Back": "congratulation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 47
    },
    {
        "Front": "オートバイ",
        "Back": "motorcycle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おかげ",
        "Back": "owing to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "おかしい",
        "Back": "strange or funny",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "億",
        "Back": "one hundred million",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 48
    },
    {
        "Front": "屋上",
        "Back": "rooftop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 49
    },
    {
        "Front": "贈り物",
        "Back": "gift",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 50
    },
    {
        "Front": "送る",
        "Back": "to send",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 51
    },
    {
        "Front": "遅れる",
        "Back": "to be late",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 52
    },
    {
        "Front": "起す",
        "Back": "to wake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 53
    },
    {
        "Front": "行う",
        "Back": "to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 54
    },
    {
        "Front": "怒る",
        "Back": "to get angry,to be angry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 55
    },
    {
        "Front": "押し入れ",
        "Back": "closet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 56
    },
    {
        "Front": "お嬢さん",
        "Back": "young lady",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 57
    },
    {
        "Front": "お宅",
        "Back": "(polite) your house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 58
    },
    {
        "Front": "落る",
        "Back": "to fall or drop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 59
    },
    {
        "Front": "おっしゃる",
        "Back": "(respectful) to say",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "夫",
        "Back": "husband",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 60
    },
    {
        "Front": "おつり",
        "Back": "change from purchase, balance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "音",
        "Back": "sound,note",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 61
    },
    {
        "Front": "落す",
        "Back": "to drop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 62
    },
    {
        "Front": "踊り",
        "Back": "a dance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 63
    },
    {
        "Front": "踊る",
        "Back": "to dance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 64
    },
    {
        "Front": "驚く",
        "Back": "to be surprised",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 65
    },
    {
        "Front": "お祭り",
        "Back": "festival",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 66
    },
    {
        "Front": "お見舞い",
        "Back": "calling on someone who is ill,enquiry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 67
    },
    {
        "Front": "お土産",
        "Back": "souvenir",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 68
    },
    {
        "Front": "思い出す",
        "Back": "to remember",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 69
    },
    {
        "Front": "思う",
        "Back": "to think,to feel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 70
    },
    {
        "Front": "おもちゃ",
        "Back": "toy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "表",
        "Back": "the front",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 71
    },
    {
        "Front": "親",
        "Back": "parents",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 72
    },
    {
        "Front": "下りる",
        "Back": "to get off",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 73
    },
    {
        "Front": "折る",
        "Back": "to break or to fold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 74
    },
    {
        "Front": "お礼",
        "Back": "expression of gratitude",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 75
    },
    {
        "Front": "折れる",
        "Back": "to break or be folded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 76
    },
    {
        "Front": "終わり",
        "Back": "the end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 77
    },
    {
        "Front": "カーテン",
        "Back": "curtain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "海岸",
        "Back": "coast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 78
    },
    {
        "Front": "会議",
        "Back": "meeting",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 79
    },
    {
        "Front": "会議室",
        "Back": "meeting room",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 80
    },
    {
        "Front": "会場",
        "Back": "assembly hall or meeting place",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 81
    },
    {
        "Front": "会話",
        "Back": "conversation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 82
    },
    {
        "Front": "帰り",
        "Back": "return",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 83
    },
    {
        "Front": "変える",
        "Back": "to change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 84
    },
    {
        "Front": "科学",
        "Back": "science",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 85
    },
    {
        "Front": "鏡",
        "Back": "mirror",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 86
    },
    {
        "Front": "掛ける",
        "Back": "to hang something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 87
    },
    {
        "Front": "飾る",
        "Back": "to decorate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 88
    },
    {
        "Front": "火事",
        "Back": "fire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 89
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガス",
        "Back": "petrol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガソリン",
        "Back": "petrol",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガソリンスタンド",
        "Back": "petrol station",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "堅/硬/固い",
        "Back": "hard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 90
    },
    {
        "Front": "形",
        "Back": "shape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 91
    },
    {
        "Front": "片付ける",
        "Back": "to tidy up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 92
    },
    {
        "Front": "課長",
        "Back": "section manager",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 93
    },
    {
        "Front": "勝つ",
        "Back": "to win",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 94
    },
    {
        "Front": "かっこう",
        "Back": "appearance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "家内",
        "Back": "housewife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 95
    },
    {
        "Front": "悲しい",
        "Back": "sad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 96
    },
    {
        "Front": "必ず",
        "Back": "certainly,necessarily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 97
    },
    {
        "Front": "お・金持ち",
        "Back": "rich man",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 98
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼女",
        "Back": "she,girlfriend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 99
    },
    {
        "Front": "壁",
        "Back": "wall",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 100
    },
    {
        "Front": "かまう",
        "Back": "to mind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "髪",
        "Back": "hair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 101
    },
    {
        "Front": "噛む",
        "Back": "to bite,to chew",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 102
    },
    {
        "Front": "通う",
        "Back": "to commute",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 103
    },
    {
        "Front": "ガラス",
        "Back": "a glass pane",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼",
        "Back": "he,boyfriend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 104
    },
    {
        "Front": "彼ら",
        "Back": "they",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 105
    },
    {
        "Front": "乾く",
        "Back": "to get dry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 106
    },
    {
        "Front": "代わり",
        "Back": "substitute,alternate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 107
    },
    {
        "Front": "変わる",
        "Back": "to change",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 108
    },
    {
        "Front": "考える",
        "Back": "to consider",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 109
    },
    {
        "Front": "関係",
        "Back": "relationship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 110
    },
    {
        "Front": "看護婦",
        "Back": "female nurse",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 111
    },
    {
        "Front": "簡単",
        "Back": "simple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 112
    },
    {
        "Front": "気",
        "Back": "spirit,mood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 113
    },
    {
        "Front": "機会",
        "Back": "opportunity",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 114
    },
    {
        "Front": "危険",
        "Back": "danger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 115
    },
    {
        "Front": "聞こえる",
        "Back": "to be heard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 116
    },
    {
        "Front": "汽車",
        "Back": "steam train",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 117
    },
    {
        "Front": "技術",
        "Back": "art,technology,skill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 118
    },
    {
        "Front": "季節",
        "Back": "season",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 119
    },
    {
        "Front": "規則",
        "Back": "regulations",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 120
    },
    {
        "Front": "きっと",
        "Back": "surely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "絹",
        "Back": "silk",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 121
    },
    {
        "Front": "厳しい",
        "Back": "strict",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 122
    },
    {
        "Front": "気分",
        "Back": "mood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 123
    },
    {
        "Front": "決る",
        "Back": "to be decided",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 124
    },
    {
        "Front": "君",
        "Back": "(informal) You (used by men towards women)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 125
    },
    {
        "Front": "決める",
        "Back": "to decide",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 126
    },
    {
        "Front": "気持ち",
        "Back": "feeling,mood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 127
    },
    {
        "Front": "着物",
        "Back": "kimono",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 128
    },
    {
        "Front": "客",
        "Back": "guest,customer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 129
    },
    {
        "Front": "急",
        "Back": "urgent, steep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 130
    },
    {
        "Front": "急行",
        "Back": "speedy, express",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 131
    },
    {
        "Front": "教育",
        "Back": "education",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 132
    },
    {
        "Front": "教会",
        "Back": "church",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 133
    },
    {
        "Front": "競争",
        "Back": "competition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 134
    },
    {
        "Front": "興味",
        "Back": "an interest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 135
    },
    {
        "Front": "近所",
        "Back": "neighbourhood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 136
    },
    {
        "Front": "具合",
        "Back": "condition,health",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 137
    },
    {
        "Front": "空気",
        "Back": "air,atmosphere",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 138
    },
    {
        "Front": "空港",
        "Back": "airport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 139
    },
    {
        "Front": "草",
        "Back": "grass",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 140
    },
    {
        "Front": "くださる",
        "Back": "(respectful) to give",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "首",
        "Back": "neck",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 141
    },
    {
        "Front": "雲",
        "Back": "cloud",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 142
    },
    {
        "Front": "比べる",
        "Back": "to compare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 143
    },
    {
        "Front": "くれる",
        "Back": "to give",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "暮れる",
        "Back": "to get dark,to come to an end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 144
    },
    {
        "Front": "毛",
        "Back": "hair or fur",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 145
    },
    {
        "Front": "計画",
        "Back": "to plan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 146
    },
    {
        "Front": "経験",
        "Back": "to experience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 147
    },
    {
        "Front": "経済",
        "Back": "finance,economy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 148
    },
    {
        "Front": "警察",
        "Back": "police",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 149
    },
    {
        "Front": "ケーキ",
        "Back": "cake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "けが・する",
        "Back": "to injure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "景色",
        "Back": "scene,landscape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 150
    },
    {
        "Front": "消しゴム",
        "Back": "eraser",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 151
    },
    {
        "Front": "下宿",
        "Back": "lodging",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 152
    },
    {
        "Front": "決して",
        "Back": "never",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 153
    },
    {
        "Front": "けれど/けれども",
        "Back": "however",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "原因",
        "Back": "cause,source",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 154
    },
    {
        "Front": "けんか・する",
        "Back": "to quarrel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "研究",
        "Back": "research",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 155
    },
    {
        "Front": "研究室",
        "Back": "study room,laboratory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 156
    },
    {
        "Front": "見物",
        "Back": "sightseeing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 157
    },
    {
        "Front": "子",
        "Back": "child",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 158
    },
    {
        "Front": "こう",
        "Back": "this way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "郊外",
        "Back": "outskirts",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 159
    },
    {
        "Front": "講義",
        "Back": "lecture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 160
    },
    {
        "Front": "工業",
        "Back": "the manufacturing industry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 161
    },
    {
        "Front": "高校",
        "Back": "high school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 162
    },
    {
        "Front": "高校生",
        "Back": "high school student",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 163
    },
    {
        "Front": "工場",
        "Back": "factory",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 164
    },
    {
        "Front": "校長",
        "Back": "headmaster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 165
    },
    {
        "Front": "交通",
        "Back": "traffic,transportation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 166
    },
    {
        "Front": "講堂",
        "Back": "auditorium",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 167
    },
    {
        "Front": "高等学校",
        "Back": "high school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 168
    },
    {
        "Front": "公務員",
        "Back": "government worker",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 169
    },
    {
        "Front": "国際",
        "Back": "international",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 170
    },
    {
        "Front": "心",
        "Back": "core,heart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 171
    },
    {
        "Front": "御主人",
        "Back": "(honorable) your husband",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 172
    },
    {
        "Front": "故障",
        "Back": "to break-down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 173
    },
    {
        "Front": "ご存じ",
        "Back": "knowing,acquaintance",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 174
    },
    {
        "Front": "答",
        "Back": "response",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 175
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごちそう",
        "Back": "a feast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "こと",
        "Back": "thing,matter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "小鳥",
        "Back": "small bird",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 176
    },
    {
        "Front": "このあいだ",
        "Back": "the other day,recently",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "このごろ",
        "Back": "these days,nowadays",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "細かい",
        "Back": "small, fine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 177
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごみ",
        "Back": "rubbish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "込む",
        "Back": "to be crowded",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 178
    },
    {
        "Front": "米",
        "Back": "uncooked rice",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 179
    },
    {
        "Front": "ごらんになる",
        "Back": "(respectful) to see",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "これから",
        "Back": "after this",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "怖い",
        "Back": "frightening",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 180
    },
    {
        "Front": "壊す",
        "Back": "to break",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 181
    },
    {
        "Front": "壊れる",
        "Back": "to be broken",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 182
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンサート",
        "Back": "concert",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "今度",
        "Back": "now,next time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 183
    },
    {
        "Front": "コンピュータ/コンピューター",
        "Back": "computer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "今夜",
        "Back": "tonight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 184
    },
    {
        "Front": "最近",
        "Back": "latest,nowadays",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 185
    },
    {
        "Front": "最後",
        "Back": "last,end",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 186
    },
    {
        "Front": "最初",
        "Back": "beginning,first",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 187
    },
    {
        "Front": "坂",
        "Back": "slope,hill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 188
    },
    {
        "Front": "探す",
        "Back": "to look for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 189
    },
    {
        "Front": "下る",
        "Back": "to get down,to descend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 190
    },
    {
        "Front": "盛ん",
        "Back": "popularity,prosperous",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 191
    },
    {
        "Front": "下げる",
        "Back": "to hang,to lower,to move back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 192
    },
    {
        "Front": "差し上げる",
        "Back": "(polite) to give",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 193
    },
    {
        "Front": "さっき",
        "Back": "some time ago",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "寂しい",
        "Back": "lonely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 194
    },
    {
        "Front": "さ来月",
        "Back": "the month after next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 195
    },
    {
        "Front": "さ来週",
        "Back": "the week after next",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 196
    },
    {
        "Front": "サラダ",
        "Back": "salad",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "騒ぐ",
        "Back": "to make noise,to be excited",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 197
    },
    {
        "Front": "触る",
        "Back": "to touch",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 198
    },
    {
        "Front": "産業",
        "Back": "industry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 199
    },
    {
        "Front": "サンダル",
        "Back": "sandal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "サンドイッチ",
        "Back": "sandwich",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "残念",
        "Back": "disappointment",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 200
    },
    {
        "Front": "市",
        "Back": "city",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 201
    },
    {
        "Front": "字",
        "Back": "character",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 202
    },
    {
        "Front": "試合",
        "Back": "match,game",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 203
    },
    {
        "Front": "仕方",
        "Back": "method",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 204
    },
    {
        "Front": "しかる",
        "Back": "a particular",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "試験",
        "Back": "examination",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 205
    },
    {
        "Front": "事故",
        "Back": "accident",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 206
    },
    {
        "Front": "地震",
        "Back": "earthquake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 207
    },
    {
        "Front": "時代",
        "Back": "era",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 208
    },
    {
        "Front": "下着",
        "Back": "underwear",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 209
    },
    {
        "Front": "支度",
        "Back": "to prepare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 210
    },
    {
        "Front": "しっかり",
        "Back": "firmly,steadily",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "失敗",
        "Back": "failure,mistake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 211
    },
    {
        "Front": "辞典",
        "Back": "dictionary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 212
    },
    {
        "Front": "品物",
        "Back": "goods",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 213
    },
    {
        "Front": "しばらく",
        "Back": "little while",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "島",
        "Back": "island",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 214
    },
    {
        "Front": "市民",
        "Back": "citizen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 215
    },
    {
        "Front": "事務所",
        "Back": "office",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 216
    },
    {
        "Front": "社会",
        "Back": "society,public",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 217
    },
    {
        "Front": "社長",
        "Back": "company president",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 218
    },
    {
        "Front": "じゃま",
        "Back": "hindrance,intrusion",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ジャム",
        "Back": "jam",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "自由",
        "Back": "freedom",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 219
    },
    {
        "Front": "習慣",
        "Back": "custom,manners",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 220
    },
    {
        "Front": "住所",
        "Back": "an address,a residence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 221
    },
    {
        "Front": "柔道",
        "Back": "judo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 222
    },
    {
        "Front": "十分",
        "Back": "enough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 223
    },
    {
        "Front": "出席",
        "Back": "to attend",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 224
    },
    {
        "Front": "出発",
        "Back": "to depart",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 225
    },
    {
        "Front": "趣味",
        "Back": "hobby",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 226
    },
    {
        "Front": "準備",
        "Back": "to prepare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 227
    },
    {
        "Front": "紹介",
        "Back": "introduction",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 228
    },
    {
        "Front": "小学校",
        "Back": "elementary school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 229
    },
    {
        "Front": "小説",
        "Back": "novel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 230
    },
    {
        "Front": "招待",
        "Back": "to invite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 231
    },
    {
        "Front": "承知",
        "Back": "to consent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 232
    },
    {
        "Front": "将来",
        "Back": "future,prospects",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 233
    },
    {
        "Front": "食事",
        "Back": "to have a meal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 234
    },
    {
        "Front": "食料品",
        "Back": "groceries",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 235
    },
    {
        "Front": "女性",
        "Back": "woman",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 236
    },
    {
        "Front": "知らせる",
        "Back": "to notify",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 237
    },
    {
        "Front": "調べる",
        "Back": "to investigate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 238
    },
    {
        "Front": "人口",
        "Back": "population",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 239
    },
    {
        "Front": "神社",
        "Back": "Shinto shrine",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 240
    },
    {
        "Front": "親切",
        "Back": "kindness",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 241
    },
    {
        "Front": "心配",
        "Back": "to worry",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 242
    },
    {
        "Front": "新聞社",
        "Back": "newspaper company",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 243
    },
    {
        "Front": "水泳",
        "Back": "swimming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 244
    },
    {
        "Front": "水道",
        "Back": "water supply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 245
    },
    {
        "Front": "ずいぶん",
        "Back": "extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "数学",
        "Back": "mathematics,arithmetic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 246
    },
    {
        "Front": "スーツ",
        "Back": "suit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スーツケース",
        "Back": "suitcase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "過ぎる",
        "Back": "to exceed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 247
    },
    {
        "Front": "すく",
        "Back": "to become empty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "スクリーン",
        "Back": "screen",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "凄い",
        "Back": "terrific",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 248
    },
    {
        "Front": "進む",
        "Back": "to make progress",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 249
    },
    {
        "Front": "すっかり",
        "Back": "completely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すっと",
        "Back": "straight,all of a sudden",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ステーキ",
        "Back": "steak",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "捨てる",
        "Back": "to throw away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 250
    },
    {
        "Front": "ステレオ",
        "Back": "stereo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "砂",
        "Back": "sand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 251
    },
    {
        "Front": "すばらしい",
        "Back": "wonderful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "滑る",
        "Back": "to slide,to slip",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 252
    },
    {
        "Front": "隅",
        "Back": "corner,nook",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 253
    },
    {
        "Front": "済む",
        "Back": "to finish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 254
    },
    {
        "Front": "すり",
        "Back": "pickpocket",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "すると",
        "Back": "then",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "生活",
        "Back": "to live",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 255
    },
    {
        "Front": "生産",
        "Back": "to produce",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 256
    },
    {
        "Front": "政治",
        "Back": "politics,government",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 257
    },
    {
        "Front": "西洋",
        "Back": "western countries",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 258
    },
    {
        "Front": "世界",
        "Back": "the world",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 259
    },
    {
        "Front": "席",
        "Back": "seat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 260
    },
    {
        "Front": "説明",
        "Back": "explanation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 261
    },
    {
        "Front": "背中",
        "Back": "back of the body",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 262
    },
    {
        "Front": "世話",
        "Back": "to look after",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 263
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぜひ",
        "Back": "without fail",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "線",
        "Back": "line",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 264
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぜんぜん",
        "Back": "not entirely (used in a negative sentence)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "戦争",
        "Back": "war",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 265
    },
    {
        "Front": "先輩",
        "Back": "senior",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 266
    },
    {
        "Front": "そう",
        "Back": "really",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "相談",
        "Back": "to discuss",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 267
    },
    {
        "Front": "育てる",
        "Back": "to rear,to bring up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 268
    },
    {
        "Front": "卒業",
        "Back": "graduation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 269
    },
    {
        "Front": "祖父",
        "Back": "grandfather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 270
    },
    {
        "Front": "祖母",
        "Back": "grandmother",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 271
    },
    {
        "Front": "ソフト",
        "Back": "soft",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それで",
        "Back": "because of that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それに",
        "Back": "moreover",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "それほど",
        "Back": "to that extent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そろそろ",
        "Back": "gradually,soon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そんな",
        "Back": "that sort of",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "そんなに",
        "Back": "so much,like that",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "退院",
        "Back": "to leave hospital",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 272
    },
    {
        "Front": "大学生",
        "Back": "university student",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 273
    },
    {
        "Front": "大事",
        "Back": "important,valuable,serious matter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 274
    },
    {
        "Front": "大体",
        "Back": "generally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 275
    },
    {
        "Front": "たいてい",
        "Back": "usually",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "タイプ",
        "Back": "type,style",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "大分",
        "Back": "greatly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 276
    },
    {
        "Front": "台風",
        "Back": "typhoon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 277
    },
    {
        "Front": "倒れる",
        "Back": "to break down",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 278
    },
    {
        "Front": "だから",
        "Back": "so,therefore",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "確か",
        "Back": "definite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 279
    },
    {
        "Front": "足す",
        "Back": "to add a number",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 280
    },
    {
        "Front": "訪ねる",
        "Back": "to visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 281
    },
    {
        "Front": "尋ねる",
        "Back": "to ask",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 282
    },
    {
        "Front": "正しい",
        "Back": "correct",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 283
    },
    {
        "Front": "畳",
        "Back": "Japanese straw mat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 284
    },
    {
        "Front": "立てる",
        "Back": "to stand something up",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 285
    },
    {
        "Front": "建てる",
        "Back": "to build",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 286
    },
    {
        "Front": "例えば",
        "Back": "for example",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 287
    },
    {
        "Front": "棚",
        "Back": "shelves",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 288
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽しみ",
        "Back": "joy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 289
    },
    {
        "Front": "楽む",
        "Back": "to enjoy oneself",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 290
    },
    {
        "Front": "たまに",
        "Back": "occasionally",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "為",
        "Back": "in order to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 291
    },
    {
        "Front": "だめ",
        "Back": "no good",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "足りる",
        "Back": "to be enough",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 292
    },
    {
        "Front": "男性",
        "Back": "male",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 293
    },
    {
        "Front": "暖房",
        "Back": "heating",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 294
    },
    {
        "Front": "血",
        "Back": "blood",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 295
    },
    {
        "Front": "チェック・する",
        "Back": "to check",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "力",
        "Back": "strength,power",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 296
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちっとも",
        "Back": "not at all (used with a negative verb)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ちゃん",
        "Back": "suffix for familiar female person",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "注意",
        "Back": "caution",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 297
    },
    {
        "Front": "中学校",
        "Back": "junior high school,middle school",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 298
    },
    {
        "Front": "注射",
        "Back": "injection",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 299
    },
    {
        "Front": "駐車場",
        "Back": "parking lot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 300
    },
    {
        "Front": "地理",
        "Back": "geography",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 301
    },
    {
        "Front": "捕まえる",
        "Back": "to seize",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 302
    },
    {
        "Front": "つき",
        "Back": "moon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "付く",
        "Back": "to be attached",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 303
    },
    {
        "Front": "漬ける",
        "Back": "to soak,to pickle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 304
    },
    {
        "Front": "都合",
        "Back": "circumstances,convenience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 305
    },
    {
        "Front": "伝える",
        "Back": "to report",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 306
    },
    {
        "Front": "続く",
        "Back": "to be continued",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 307
    },
    {
        "Front": "続ける",
        "Back": "to continue",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 308
    },
    {
        "Front": "包む",
        "Back": "to wrap",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 309
    },
    {
        "Front": "妻",
        "Back": "(humble) wife",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 310
    },
    {
        "Front": "つもり",
        "Back": "intention",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "釣る",
        "Back": "to fish",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 311
    },
    {
        "Front": "連れる",
        "Back": "to lead",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 312
    },
    {
        "Front": "丁寧",
        "Back": "polite",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 313
    },
    {
        "Front": "テキスト",
        "Back": "text,text book",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "適当",
        "Back": "suitability",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 314
    },
    {
        "Front": "できるだけ",
        "Back": "as much as possible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "手伝う",
        "Back": "to assist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 315
    },
    {
        "Front": "テニス",
        "Back": "tennis",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "手袋",
        "Back": "glove",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 316
    },
    {
        "Front": "寺",
        "Back": "temple",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 317
    },
    {
        "Front": "点",
        "Back": "point,dot",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 318
    },
    {
        "Front": "店員",
        "Back": "shop assistant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 319
    },
    {
        "Front": "天気予報",
        "Back": "weather forecast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 320
    },
    {
        "Front": "電灯",
        "Back": "electric light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 321
    },
    {
        "Front": "電報",
        "Back": "telegram",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 322
    },
    {
        "Front": "展覧会",
        "Back": "exhibition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 323
    },
    {
        "Front": "都",
        "Back": "metropolitan",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 324
    },
    {
        "Front": "道具",
        "Back": "tool,means",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 325
    },
    {
        "Front": "とうとう",
        "Back": "finally, after all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "動物園",
        "Back": "zoo",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 326
    },
    {
        "Front": "遠く",
        "Back": "distant",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 327
    },
    {
        "Front": "通る",
        "Back": "to go through",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 328
    },
    {
        "Front": "特に",
        "Back": "particularly,especially",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 329
    },
    {
        "Front": "特別",
        "Back": "special",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 330
    },
    {
        "Front": "とこや",
        "Back": "barber",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "途中",
        "Back": "on the way",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 331
    },
    {
        "Front": "特急",
        "Back": "limited express train (faster than an express train)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 332
    },
    {
        "Front": "届ける",
        "Back": "to reach",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 333
    },
    {
        "Front": "泊まる",
        "Back": "to lodge at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 334
    },
    {
        "Front": "止める",
        "Back": "to stop something",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 335
    },
    {
        "Front": "取り替える",
        "Back": "to exchange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 336
    },
    {
        "Front": "泥棒",
        "Back": "thief",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 337
    },
    {
        "Front": "どんどん",
        "Back": "more and more",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "直す",
        "Back": "to fix,to repair",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 338
    },
    {
        "Front": "直る",
        "Back": "to be fixed,to be repaired",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 339
    },
    {
        "Front": "治る",
        "Back": "to be cured,to heal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 340
    },
    {
        "Front": "中々",
        "Back": "considerably",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 341
    },
    {
        "Front": "泣く",
        "Back": "to weep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 342
    },
    {
        "Front": "無くなる",
        "Back": "to disappear,to get lost",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 343
    },
    {
        "Front": "亡くなる",
        "Back": "to die",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 345
    },
    {
        "Front": "投げる",
        "Back": "to throw or cast away",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 344
    },
    {
        "Front": "なさる",
        "Back": "(respectful) to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "鳴る",
        "Back": "to sound",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 346
    },
    {
        "Front": "なるべく",
        "Back": "as much as possible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "なるほど",
        "Back": "now I understand",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "慣れる",
        "Back": "to grow accustomed to",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 347
    },
    {
        "Front": "におい",
        "Back": "a smell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "苦い",
        "Back": "bitter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 348
    },
    {
        "Front": "二階建て",
        "Back": "two storied",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 349
    },
    {
        "Front": "逃げる",
        "Back": "to escape",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 350
    },
    {
        "Front": "日記",
        "Back": "journal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 351
    },
    {
        "Front": "入院",
        "Back": "to hospitalise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 352
    },
    {
        "Front": "入学",
        "Back": "to enter school or university",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 353
    },
    {
        "Front": "似る",
        "Back": "to be similar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 354
    },
    {
        "Front": "人形",
        "Back": "doll, figure",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 356
    },
    {
        "Front": "盗む",
        "Back": "to steal",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 355
    },
    {
        "Front": "塗る",
        "Back": "to paint,to plaster",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 357
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぬれる",
        "Back": "to get wet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ねだん",
        "Back": "price",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "熱",
        "Back": "fever",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 358
    },
    {
        "Front": "ねっしん",
        "Back": "enthusiasm",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "寝坊",
        "Back": "sleeping in late",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 359
    },
    {
        "Front": "眠い",
        "Back": "sleepy",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 360
    },
    {
        "Front": "眠る",
        "Back": "to sleep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 361
    },
    {
        "Front": "残る",
        "Back": "to remain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 362
    },
    {
        "Front": "のど",
        "Back": "throat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗り換える",
        "Back": "to change between buses or trains",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 363
    },
    {
        "Front": "乗り物",
        "Back": "vehicle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 364
    },
    {
        "Front": "葉",
        "Back": "leaf",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 365
    },
    {
        "Front": "場合",
        "Back": "situation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 366
    },
    {
        "Front": "パート",
        "Back": "part time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "倍",
        "Back": "double",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 367
    },
    {
        "Front": "拝見",
        "Back": "(humble) to look at",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 368
    },
    {
        "Front": "歯医者",
        "Back": "dentist",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 369
    },
    {
        "Front": "運ぶ",
        "Back": "to transport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 370
    },
    {
        "Front": "始める",
        "Back": "to begin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 371
    },
    {
        "Front": "場所",
        "Back": "location",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 372
    },
    {
        "Front": "はず",
        "Back": "it should be so",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "恥ずかしい",
        "Back": "embarrassed",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 373
    },
    {
        "Front": "パソコン",
        "Back": "personal computer",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "発音",
        "Back": "pronunciation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 374
    },
    {
        "Front": "はっきり",
        "Back": "clearly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "花見",
        "Back": "cherry-blossom viewing",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 375
    },
    {
        "Front": "林",
        "Back": "woods,forester",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 376
    },
    {
        "Front": "払う",
        "Back": "to pay",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 377
    },
    {
        "Front": "番組",
        "Back": "television or radio program",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 378
    },
    {
        "Front": "反対",
        "Back": "opposition",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 379
    },
    {
        "Front": "ハンドバッグ",
        "Back": "handbag　",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "日",
        "Back": "day, sun",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 380
    },
    {
        "Front": "火",
        "Back": "fire",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 381
    },
    {
        "Front": "ピアノ",
        "Back": "piano",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷える",
        "Back": "to grow cold",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 382
    },
    {
        "Front": "光",
        "Back": "light",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 383
    },
    {
        "Front": "光る",
        "Back": "to shine,to glitter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 384
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き出し",
        "Back": "drawer,drawing out",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 385
    },
    {
        "Front": "引き出す",
        "Back": "to withdraw",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 386
    },
    {
        "Front": "ひげ",
        "Back": "beard",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "飛行場",
        "Back": "airport",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 387
    },
    {
        "Front": "久しぶり",
        "Back": "after a long time",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 388
    },
    {
        "Front": "美術館",
        "Back": "art gallery",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 389
    },
    {
        "Front": "非常に",
        "Back": "extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 390
    },
    {
        "Front": "びっくり・する",
        "Back": "to be surprised",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "引っ越す",
        "Back": "to move house",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 391
    },
    {
        "Front": "必要",
        "Back": "necessary",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 392
    },
    {
        "Front": "ひどい",
        "Back": "awful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "開く",
        "Back": "to open an event",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 393
    },
    {
        "Front": "ビル",
        "Back": "building or bill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼間",
        "Back": "daytime,during the day",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 394
    },
    {
        "Front": "昼休み",
        "Back": "noon break",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 395
    },
    {
        "Front": "拾う",
        "Back": "to pick up,to gather",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 396
    },
    {
        "Front": "ファックス",
        "Back": "fax",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "増える",
        "Back": "to increase",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 397
    },
    {
        "Front": "深い",
        "Back": "deep",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 398
    },
    {
        "Front": "複雑",
        "Back": "complexity,complication",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 399
    },
    {
        "Front": "復習",
        "Back": "revision",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 400
    },
    {
        "Front": "部長",
        "Back": "head of a section",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 401
    },
    {
        "Front": "普通",
        "Back": "usually, or a train that stops at every station",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 402
    },
    {
        "Front": "ぶどう",
        "Back": "grapes",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "太る",
        "Back": "to become fat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 403
    },
    {
        "Front": "布団",
        "Back": "Japanese bedding, futon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 404
    },
    {
        "Front": "舟",
        "Back": "ship",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 405
    },
    {
        "Front": "不便",
        "Back": "inconvenience",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 406
    },
    {
        "Front": "踏む",
        "Back": "to step on",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 407
    },
    {
        "Front": "降り出す",
        "Back": "to start to rain",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 408
    },
    {
        "Front": "プレゼント",
        "Back": "present",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "文化",
        "Back": "culture",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 409
    },
    {
        "Front": "文学",
        "Back": "literature",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 410
    },
    {
        "Front": "文法",
        "Back": "grammar",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 411
    },
    {
        "Front": "別",
        "Back": "different",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 412
    },
    {
        "Front": "ベル",
        "Back": "bell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "変",
        "Back": "strange",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 413
    },
    {
        "Front": "返事",
        "Back": "reply",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 414
    },
    {
        "Front": "貿易",
        "Back": "trade",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 415
    },
    {
        "Front": "放送",
        "Back": "to broadcast",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 416
    },
    {
        "Front": "法律",
        "Back": "law",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 417
    },
    {
        "Front": "僕",
        "Back": "I (used by males)",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 418
    },
    {
        "Front": "星",
        "Back": "star",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 419
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほど",
        "Back": "extent",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほとんど",
        "Back": "mostly",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "ほめる",
        "Back": "to praise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "翻訳",
        "Back": "translation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 420
    },
    {
        "Front": "参る",
        "Back": "(humble) to go,to come",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 421
    },
    {
        "Front": "負ける",
        "Back": "to lose",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 422
    },
    {
        "Front": "まじめ",
        "Back": "serious",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "まず",
        "Back": "first of all",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "または",
        "Back": "or,otherwise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "間違える",
        "Back": "to make a mistake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 423
    },
    {
        "Front": "間に合う",
        "Back": "to be in time for",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 424
    },
    {
        "Front": "周り",
        "Back": "surroundings",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 425
    },
    {
        "Front": "回る",
        "Back": "to go around",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 426
    },
    {
        "Front": "漫画",
        "Back": "comic",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 427
    },
    {
        "Front": "真中",
        "Back": "middle",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 428
    },
    {
        "Front": "見える",
        "Back": "to be in sight",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 429
    },
    {
        "Front": "湖",
        "Back": "lake",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 430
    },
    {
        "Front": "味噌",
        "Back": "bean paste",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 431
    },
    {
        "Front": "見つかる",
        "Back": "to be discovered",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 432
    },
    {
        "Front": "見つける",
        "Back": "to discover",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 433
    },
    {
        "Front": "皆",
        "Back": "everybody",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 434
    },
    {
        "Front": "港",
        "Back": "harbour",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 435
    },
    {
        "Front": "向かう",
        "Back": "to face",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 436
    },
    {
        "Front": "迎える",
        "Back": "to go out to meet",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 437
    },
    {
        "Front": "昔",
        "Back": "olden days, former",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 438
    },
    {
        "Front": "虫",
        "Back": "insect",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 439
    },
    {
        "Front": "息子",
        "Back": "(humble) son",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 440
    },
    {
        "Front": "娘",
        "Back": "(humble) daughter",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 441
    },
    {
        "Front": "無理",
        "Back": "impossible",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 442
    },
    {
        "Front": "召し上がる",
        "Back": "(polite) to eat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 443
    },
    {
        "Front": "珍しい",
        "Back": "rare",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 444
    },
    {
        "Front": "申し上げる",
        "Back": "(humble) to say,to tell",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 445
    },
    {
        "Front": "申す",
        "Back": "(humble) to be called,to say",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 446
    },
    {
        "Front": "もうすぐ",
        "Back": "soon",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "もし",
        "Back": "if",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "もちろん",
        "Back": "of course",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "もっとも",
        "Back": "extremely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "戻る",
        "Back": "to turn back",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 447
    },
    {
        "Front": "木綿",
        "Back": "cotton",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 448
    },
    {
        "Front": "もらう",
        "Back": "to receive",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "森",
        "Back": "forest",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 449
    },
    {
        "Front": "焼く",
        "Back": "to bake,to grill",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 450
    },
    {
        "Front": "約束",
        "Back": "promise",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 451
    },
    {
        "Front": "役に立つ",
        "Back": "to be helpful",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 452
    },
    {
        "Front": "焼ける",
        "Back": "to burn,to be roasted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 453
    },
    {
        "Front": "優しい",
        "Back": "kind",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 454
    },
    {
        "Front": "痩せる",
        "Back": "to become thin",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 455
    },
    {
        "Front": "やっと",
        "Back": "at last",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "やはり/やっぱり",
        "Back": "as I thought,absolutely",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "止む",
        "Back": "to stop",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 456
    },
    {
        "Front": "柔らかい",
        "Back": "soft",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 457
    },
    {
        "Front": "湯",
        "Back": "hot water",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 458
    },
    {
        "Front": "輸出",
        "Back": "to export",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 459
    },
    {
        "Front": "輸入",
        "Back": "to import",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 460
    },
    {
        "Front": "指",
        "Back": "finger",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 461
    },
    {
        "Front": "指輪",
        "Back": "finger ring",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 462
    },
    {
        "Front": "夢",
        "Back": "dream",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 463
    },
    {
        "Front": "揺れる",
        "Back": "to shake,to sway",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 464
    },
    {
        "Front": "用",
        "Back": "use",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 465
    },
    {
        "Front": "用意",
        "Back": "preparation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 466
    },
    {
        "Front": "用事",
        "Back": "things to do",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 467
    },
    {
        "Front": "汚れる",
        "Back": "to get dirty",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 468
    },
    {
        "Front": "予習",
        "Back": "preparation for a lesson",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 469
    },
    {
        "Front": "予定",
        "Back": "arrangement",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 470
    },
    {
        "Front": "予約",
        "Back": "reservation",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 471
    },
    {
        "Front": "寄る",
        "Back": "to visit",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 472
    },
    {
        "Front": "喜ぶ",
        "Back": "to be delighted",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 473
    },
    {
        "Front": "よろしい",
        "Back": "(respectful) OK,all right",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "理由",
        "Back": "reason",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 474
    },
    {
        "Front": "利用",
        "Back": "utilization",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 475
    },
    {
        "Front": "両方",
        "Back": "both sides",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 476
    },
    {
        "Front": "旅館",
        "Back": "Japanese hotel",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 477
    },
    {
        "Front": "留守",
        "Back": "absence",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 478
    },
    {
        "Front": "冷房",
        "Back": "air conditioning",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 479
    },
    {
        "Front": "歴史",
        "Back": "history",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 480
    },
    {
        "Front": "レジ",
        "Back": "register",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "レポート/リポート",
        "Back": "report",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "連絡",
        "Back": "contact",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 481
    },
    {
        "Front": "ワープロ",
        "Back": "word processor",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": null
    },
    {
        "Front": "沸かす",
        "Back": "to boil,to heat",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 482
    },
    {
        "Front": "別れる",
        "Back": "to separate",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 483
    },
    {
        "Front": "沸く",
        "Back": "to boil, to grow hot,to get excited",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 484
    },
    {
        "Front": "訳",
        "Back": "meaning,reason",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 485
    },
    {
        "Front": "忘れ物",
        "Back": "lost article",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 486
    },
    {
        "Front": "笑う",
        "Back": "to laugh,to smile",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 487
    },
    {
        "Front": "割合",
        "Back": "rate,ratio,percentage",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 488
    },
    {
        "Front": "割れる",
        "Back": "to break",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 489
    },
    {
        "Front": "泳ぎ方",
        "Back": "way of swimming",
        "Tags": [],
        "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-eng",
        "HiraganaIndex": 490
    }
]